We ship worldwide

Dealer Locations

Contact Us

Wishlist

* [
    
    English](#)
    * [
        
        Français](https://www.agragps.com/fr/privacy-statement-au/)
    * [
        
        Deutsch](https://www.agragps.com/de/privacy-statement-au/)
    * [
        
        Polski](https://www.agragps.com/pl/privacy-statement-au/)
    * [
        
        Português](https://www.agragps.com/pt-br/privacy-statement-au/)
    * [
        
        Español](https://www.agragps.com/es/privacy-statement-au/)

+1 (825) 247-2477

[](tel:%20+1%20(825)%20247-2477)

* No products in the cart.

Shopping Cart

* No products in the cart.

Top Searches:

Menu

Close

    Best Fit with

    CRG – GPS Receiver/Bridge

    EUR € 4,800.00 – € 5,550.00

    EUR € 5,500.00 – € 6,150.00
    
    BRIDGE

    ~€ 3,380.00~ Original price was: € 3,380.00.€ 3,150.00Current price is: € 3,150.00.

    [Versatile JD-BRIDGE – Versatile Articulated, Versatile RowCrop Bridge Compatible with John Deere Display](https://www.agragps.com/product/versatile-jd-bridge-versatile-articulated-versatile-rowcrop-bridge-compatible-with-john-deere-display/)
    
    EUR € 3,150.00
    
    ITC Extend

    Rated **5.00** out of 5
    
    € 620.00
    
    Accessories

    € 2,690.00

    ~€ 140.00~ Original price was: € 140.00.€ 130.00Current price is: € 130.00.

    € 130.00

All Categories

* All Categories
    
* Bridges
    
* Accessories
    
* AGCO
    
* CAT
    
* Claas
    
* CNH
    
* Combines
    
* Deutz
    
* Fendt
    
* GPS
    
* Horsch
    
* ITCExtend
    
* JCB
    
* Krone
    
* Kubota
    
* Massey Ferguson
    
* Mounts
    
* Rogator
    
* RTK
    
* Sprayers
    
* Swathers
    
* Tractors
    
* Valtra
    
* Versatile

Menu

    Best Fit with

    CRG – GPS Receiver/Bridge

    EUR € 4,800.00 – € 5,550.00

    EUR € 5,500.00 – € 6,150.00
    
    BRIDGE

    ~€ 3,380.00~ Original price was: € 3,380.00.€ 3,150.00Current price is: € 3,150.00.

    [Versatile JD-BRIDGE – Versatile Articulated, Versatile RowCrop Bridge Compatible with John Deere Display](https://www.agragps.com/product/versatile-jd-bridge-versatile-articulated-versatile-rowcrop-bridge-compatible-with-john-deere-display/)
    
    EUR € 3,150.00
    
    ITC Extend

    Rated **5.00** out of 5
    
    € 620.00
    
    Accessories

    EUR € 4,800.00 – € 5,550.00

    EUR € 80.00

    € 130.00

_

_English

* [_

    _Français](https://www.agragps.com/fr/privacy-statement-au/)
* [_

    _Deutsch](https://www.agragps.com/de/privacy-statement-au/)
* [_

    _Polski](https://www.agragps.com/pl/privacy-statement-au/)
* [_

    _Português](https://www.agragps.com/pt-br/privacy-statement-au/)
* [_

    _Español](https://www.agragps.com/es/privacy-statement-au/)

Top Searches:

* No products in the cart.

_This privacy statement was last changed on June 10, 2022, last checked on June 10, 2022, and applies to citizens of Australia._  

In this privacy statement, we explain what we do with the data we obtain about you via [https://www.agragps.com](https://www.agragps.com/). We recommend you carefully read this statement. In our processing we comply with the requirements of privacy legislation. That means, among other things, that:

* we clearly state the purposes for which we process personal data. We do this by means of this privacy statement;
* we aim to limit our collection of personal data to only the personal data required for legitimate purposes;
* we first request your explicit consent to process your personal data in cases requiring your consent;
* we take appropriate security measures to protect your personal data and also require this from parties that process personal data on our behalf;
* we respect your right to access your personal data or have it corrected or deleted, at your request.

If you have any questions, or want to know exactly what data we keep of you, please contact us.

1\. Purpose and categories of data
----------------------------------

We may collect or receive personal information for a number of purposes connected with our business operations which may include the following: (click to expand)

### 1.1 Contact - Through phone, mail, email and/or webforms

The following categories of data are collected

* A first and last name
* Account name or alias
* A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town
* An email address
* A telephone number
* IP address
* Geolocation data

Retention period

We retain this data upon termination of the service for the following number of months: 6

### 1.2 Payments

The following categories of data are collected

* A first and last name
* Account name or alias
* A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town
* An email address
* A telephone number
* IP address
* Financial information such as bank account number or credit card number
* Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered
* Geolocation data

Retention period

Upon termination of the service we retain this data for the following period: until the warranty, or service of the product lifetime expires.

### 1.3 Registering an account

The following categories of data are collected

* A first and last name
* Account name or alias
* A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town
* An email address
* A telephone number
* IP address
* Financial information such as bank account number or credit card number
* Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered
* Geolocation data

Retention period

Upon termination of the service we retain this data for the following period: until the warranty, or service of the product lifetime expires.

### 1.4 To support services or products that a customer wants to buy or has purchased

The following categories of data are collected

* A first and last name
* Account name or alias
* A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town
* An email address
* A telephone number
* IP address
* Financial information such as bank account number or credit card number
* Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered
* Geolocation data

Retention period

Upon termination of the service we retain this data for the following period: until the warranty, or service of the product lifetime expires.

### 1.5 To be able to comply with legal obligations

The collection is required or authorized by the following law or court/tribunal order:

Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada  
  
The Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada oversees our personal information handling practices. If any privacy concerns are not addressed to your satisfaction you may contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada for further guidance:  
  
By Phone: 1-800-282-1376 or 613-995-8210  
  
By Fax: 613-947-6850  
  
By E-mail: info@privcom.gc.ca  
  
Website: www.privcom.gc.ca

The following categories of data are collected

* A first and last name
* Account name or alias
* A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town
* An email address
* A telephone number
* IP address
* Financial information such as bank account number or credit card number
* Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered
* Geolocation data

Retention period

Upon termination of the service we retain this data for the following period: until the warranty, or service of the product lifetime expires.

### 1.6 Compiling and analyzing statistics for website improvement.

The following categories of data are collected

* A first and last name
* Account name or alias
* A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town
* An email address
* A telephone number
* IP address
* Financial information such as bank account number or credit card number
* Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered
* Geolocation data

Retention period

Upon termination of the service we retain this data for the following period: until the warranty, or service of the product lifetime expires.

### 1.7 To be able to offer personalized products and services

The following categories of data are collected

* A first and last name
* Account name or alias
* A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town
* An email address
* A telephone number
* IP address
* Financial information such as bank account number or credit card number
* Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered
* Geolocation data

Retention period

Upon termination of the service we retain this data for the following period: until the warranty, or service of the product lifetime expires.

### 1.8 Deliveries

The following categories of data are collected

* A first and last name
* Account name or alias
* A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town
* An email address
* A telephone number
* IP address
* Financial information such as bank account number or credit card number
* Commercial information, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered
* Geolocation data

Retention period

Upon termination of the service we retain this data for the following period: until the warranty, or service of the product lifetime expires.

2\. Sharing with other parties
------------------------------

We do not share data with third parties.

3\. Disclosure practices
------------------------

We disclose personal information if we are required by law or by a court order, in response to a law enforcement agency, to the extent permitted under other provisions of law, to provide information, or for an investigation on a matter related to public safety.

If our website or organisation is taken over, sold, or involved in a merger or acquisition, your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and will be passed on to the new owners.

4\. What if you don't provide us with your personal information?
----------------------------------------------------------------

If you don't provide us with your personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the information, products or assistance that you are seeking.

5\. How we respond to Do Not Track signals & Global Privacy Control
-------------------------------------------------------------------

Our website responds to and supports the Do Not Track (DNT) header request field. If you turn DNT on in your browser, those preferences are communicated to us in the HTTP request header, and we will not track your browsing behavior.

6\. Cookies
-----------

Our website uses cookies. For more information about cookies, please refer to our Cookie Policy on our [Cookie Policy (AU)](https://www.agragps.com/cookie-policy-au/) webpage. 

7\. Security
------------

We are committed to the security of personal data. We take appropriate security measures to limit abuse of and unauthorized access to personal data. This ensures that only the necessary persons have access to your data, that access to the data is protected, and that our security measures are regularly reviewed.

8\. Third party websites
------------------------

This privacy statement does not apply to third party websites connected by links on our website. We cannot guarantee that these third parties handle your personal data in a reliable or secure manner. We recommend you read the privacy statements of these websites prior to making use of these websites.

9\. Amendments to this privacy statement
----------------------------------------

We reserve the right to make amendments to this privacy statement. It is recommended that you consult this privacy statement regularly in order to be aware of any changes. In addition, we will actively inform you wherever possible.

10\. Accessing and modifying your data
--------------------------------------

If you have any questions or want to know which personal data we have about you, please contact us. Please make sure to always clearly state who you are, so that we can be certain that we do not modify or delete any data of the wrong person. We shall provide the requested information only upon receipt of a verifiable consumer request. You can contact us by using the information below. You have the following rights:

10.1 You have the following rights with respect to your personal data

1. You may submit a request for access to the data we process about you.
2. You may request an overview, in a commonly used format, of the data we process about you.
3. You may request correction or deletion of the data if it is incorrect or not or no longer relevant for any purpose under the Privacy Act.

11\. Children
-------------

Our website is not designed to attract children and it is not our intent to collect personal data from children under the age of consent in their country of residence. We therefore request that children under the age of consent do not submit any personal data to us.

12\. Contact details
--------------------

Agra-GPS Ltd.  
Box 2585  
Stony Plain, AB  
Canada  
Canada  
Website: [https://www.agragps.com](https://www.agragps.com/)  
Email: moc.spgarga@lepuehj  
Toll free phone number: 7809904052  
Phone number: +1 7809904052

We have appointed a contact person for the organization’s policies and practices and to whom complaints or inquiries can be forwarded:  
Compliance Officer  
Agra-GPS Ltd.  
Box 2585  
Stony Plain, AB  
Canada

* Address:
* Box 2585 Stony Plain
* AB T7Z 1X9
* Canada

* Phone: [+1 (825) 247-2477](tel:+1 (825) 247-2477)
* Email: [info@agragps.com](mailto:info@agragps.com)
* Web: https://www.agragps.com/

AGRA GPS

LEGAL/SUPPORT

© Copyright Agra-GPS 2023.  
All product names, logos, and brands remain the property of their respective owners.

Manage Cookie Consent

To provide the best experiences, we use technologies like cookies to store and/or access device information. Consenting to these technologies will allow us to process data such as browsing behavior or unique IDs on this site. Not consenting or withdrawing consent, may adversely affect certain features and functions.

Functional  Functional Always active

The technical storage or access is strictly necessary for the legitimate purpose of enabling the use of a specific service explicitly requested by the subscriber or user, or for the sole purpose of carrying out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network.

Preferences  Preferences

The technical storage or access is necessary for the legitimate purpose of storing preferences that are not requested by the subscriber or user.

Statistics  Statistics

The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for statistical purposes. The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for anonymous statistical purposes. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, information stored or retrieved for this purpose alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

Marketing  Marketing

The technical storage or access is required to create user profiles to send advertising, or to track the user on a website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.

Accept Deny View preferences Save preferences [View preferences](#)

Manage Cookie Consent

To provide the best experiences, we use technologies like cookies to store and/or access device information. Consenting to these technologies will allow us to process data such as browsing behavior or unique IDs on this site. Not consenting or withdrawing consent, may adversely affect certain features and functions.

Functional  Functional Always active

The technical storage or access is strictly necessary for the legitimate purpose of enabling the use of a specific service explicitly requested by the subscriber or user, or for the sole purpose of carrying out the transmission of a communication over an electronic communications network.

Preferences  Preferences

The technical storage or access is necessary for the legitimate purpose of storing preferences that are not requested by the subscriber or user.

Statistics  Statistics

The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for statistical purposes. The technical storage or access that is used exclusively for anonymous statistical purposes. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, information stored or retrieved for this purpose alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

Marketing  Marketing

The technical storage or access is required to create user profiles to send advertising, or to track the user on a website or across several websites for similar marketing purposes.

Accept Deny View preferences Save preferences [View preferences](#)

Manage consent Manage consent

By accessing this website you, you are agreeing to the Terms of Use of this website & Cookie usage. Our website uses tiny cookies from third party services to improve your browsing experience.

Review Terms of Service I Understand

Close

Privacy Preferences

When you visit our website, it may store information through your browser from specific services, usually in form of cookies. Here you can change your privacy preferences. Please note that blocking some types of cookies may impact your experience on our website and the services we offer.  
  
Please read these Terms of Service (“Terms”) carefully before you begin using Our Products and Services or any Third Party Services. By clicking “Login”, “Create Account”, “Sign In” “Sign Up”, creating a user account, placing an order, or otherwise using the Products and Services, you agree to accept and be bound by these Terms, along with the AGRA GPS End User License Agreement, AGRA GPS Privacy Policy, and the AGRA GPS Privacy Statement, which are all taken together and incorporated by reference into these Terms, and govern Your use of the Products and Services and constitute a binding legal agreement between You and AGRA GPS, (the “Agreement”).  
  
View Terms of Service & Accepted Agreement https://www.agragps.com/terms/

Privacy Policy

You have read and agreed to our privacy policy

Required

Notice of Terms of Use

Please review the terms of use while you are using this website: [view terms](https://www.agra-gps.com/terms).

Required

Save Preferences
